[
    {
      "question": "C# is a programming language, developed by ___.",
      "answers": [
        "Oracle",
        "Microsoft",
        "GNU project",
        "Google"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "C# runs on the ___.",
      "answers": [
        ".NET Framework",
        "Java Virtual Machine",
        "Both A. and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "C# programming language is used to develop -",
      "answers": [
        "Web apps",
        "Desktop apps",
        "Mobiles apps",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Is C# an object-oriented programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Is C++ an alias of C#?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the extension of a C# language file?",
      "answers": [
        ".c",
        ".cpp",
        ".cs",
        ".csp"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the founder of C# programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Anders Hejlsberg",
        "Douglas Crockford",
        "Rasmus Lerdorf",
        "Brendan Eich"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Is C# a type safe programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Is C# a structured programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "CLR stands for ___.",
      "answers": [
        "Common Type System",
        "Common Language Specification",
        "Common Language Runtime",
        "Java Virtual Machine"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    }
  ]